1. if (individualRun)
5. if (true)
1. selectOptionByLabel(findTestObject("Page_CuraAppointment/lst_Facility"), "Hongkong CURA Healthcare Center", false)
5. check(findTestObject("Page_CuraAppointment/chk_Medicaid"))
9. check(findTestObject("Page_CuraAppointment/chk_Readmission"))
13. setText(findTestObject("Page_CuraAppointment/txt_VisitDate"), "27/12/2016")
17. setText(findTestObject("Page_CuraAppointment/txt_Comment"), "Please make appointment as soon as possible.")
9. comment("When he fills in valid information in Appointment page")
13. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_CuraAppointment/btn_BookAppointment"))
17. verifyTextPresent("Appointment Confirmation", false)
21. comment("Then he should be able to book a new appointment")
25. if (true)
1. verifyMatch("Hongkong CURA Healthcare Center", getText(findTestObject("Page_AppointmentConfirmation/lbl_Facility")), false)
5. verifyMatch("Yes", getText(findTestObject("Page_AppointmentConfirmation/lbl_HospitalReadmission")), false)
9. verifyMatch("Medicaid", getText(findTestObject("Page_AppointmentConfirmation/lbl_Program")), false)
13. verifyMatch("27/12/2016", getText(findTestObject("Page_AppointmentConfirmation/lbl_VisitDate")), false)
17. verifyMatch("Please make appointment as soon as possible.", getText(findTestObject("Page_AppointmentConfirmation/lbl_Comment")), false)